

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Mr. Alunni

NATIONALITY: Italian

SUMMARY

I am a Professional Civil Technician. I have lengthy experience in the design, detailing and supervision to construction of residential buildings, roads, sewerage, stormwater, water reticulations and irrigation systems acquired in Italy, South Africa and other African Countries. I have been involved in a large number of assignments which have been successfully completed to date, ranging from major fast track commercial and industrial projects to infrastructure projects at various levels. I have experience in operating within the tight financial disciplines imposed by ambitious budgets which I have helped to plan as well as methodical administration to deadlines. My own cosmopolitan background and analytical interests in other cultures, together with a command of several European languages, have also left me confident in handling negotiations that require the reconciliation of different national approaches to otherwise common problems.

EDUCATION

Diploma di Geometra – Instituto Technico Per Geometri Perugia (Italy), 1964

Above Diploma obtained after passing a State Examination on the following subjects: Architectural and Structural Design of Building, Roads and Hydraulic Constructions – Land Survey – Economics and Property evaluation – Civil Law

EMPLOYMENT RECORD/PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

03/06 to pres. HLANGANANI ENGINEERS - Mulbarton (Joahannesburg)

Consulting Civil Engineers and Project Managers

Design, Detailing of Road, Sewerage, Water Supply and Storm Water reticulations

1996 to 05 NDODANA CONSULTING ENGINEERS - Craighall (Johannesburg)

Consulting Civil Engineers



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Design, Detailing & Site Supervision to Construction of Road, Sewerage, Water Supply and Storm Water reticulations

1992 - 1995 **VENCOTECH cc.** - Tohoyandou - Venda (South Africa)

Own Consulting practice for technical and managerial support to local Developing Communities.

Design and Supervision to Construction of Rural Roads, Schools, Clinics, Small irrigation schemes, Village sanitation and Water Supply schemes, including on-job training of local labor

1988 -1991 DU TOIT, BECKER & ASSOCIATES

Consulting Civil Engineers, - (Johannesburg)

Resident Engineer responsible for the supervision to construction of Roads, Sewerage, Storm water and Water reticulation of Lenasia Ext 13 Township (Johannesburg South) 1600 Stands

1984 - 1987 BONIFICA Spa - Rome - Maputo Branch (MOZAMBIQUE)

Senior expert in the field of agricultural hydraulics and construction, appointed as advisor to the Mozambican Ministry of Agriculture to implement a project of rehabilitation of farms destroyed by the 1984 cyclone, including design and supervision to Construction of various small scale irrigation systems and related civil works as well as the management of the State firm created for the receiving, distribution and installation of the construction materials.

1981 - 1983 AGROTECH Spa - Rome -Maseru Branch (LESOTHO)

Construction Specialist appointed as Project Manager responsible for the design and construction with local labor force of the infrastructures of the Lesotho Feed-Lot in Maseru (Lesotho) -Capacity 12 000 Heads per year.

1977 -1980 ITALIAN MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS - Rabat (MOROCCO)

(Department of Co-operation with Developing Countries)



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

 $\label{lemail:consultant@londonresearch international.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.$

Senior Construction and Land Survey Expert appointed as Technical Advisor to the Moroccan Ministry of Agriculture for the subdivision of cooperative farms and construction of farmer's residence houses

1965 - 1977 F.LLI PISELLI Srl - Perugia (Italy)

Civil, Building and Road Contractors;

Site Agent responsible for construction of various Roads, Township services and Industrial Buildings

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS		
n/a		
PUBLICATIONS		
n/a		
LANGUAGES		

Italian, English, French, Portuguese, Spanish